

Asmat AliFull stack Developer

My Contact

□ asmat689@gmail.com

(+023439602946

Mingora Swat Pakistan

https://imasmat.w3spaces.com

Skills

- project Management
- Html ,Css,Bootstrap
- javaScript,jQuery,Ajax
- PHP,laravel, Vue.js
- Rest Api's
- designing
- Teaching
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Computer operator

Educations

- khpalKor model school & collage pre-engineering
 Completed in 2018
- Collage of modren science
 Diploma information Technology (DIT)

 Completed in 2017
- Virtual University Of Pakistan
 Bachelor of computer science (BS)

 Completed in 2022

LANGUAGES

pashto, Urdu ,English

Certificate

police driving license school Presentation 1st position

About Me

Hey I'm Asmat, a developer with 2+ years experience writing HTML,Css,Bootstrap,javascript,jquery, PHP,Sql laravel & vue.js.

I specialize in building web apps using frameworks like Laravel, and Vue.js.

I work remotely with teams to build appropriate, elegant and reliable solutions to complex problems – helping global companies,

Professional Experience

Zarnain Graphic Designing 2019 – 2020

Key responsibilities:

- Make designing for shop and Hospital & ect
- printing press design and brochure design
- school Paper and documents, Urdu Writing

Webdsoft Company Limit| full stack/Internship

2020 - 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Develop responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, jQuery/JavaScript Php
- complete Project Online Charity Management (final year Project)
- Complete Shop project (mohib designing shop)

Said Information technology| Full Stack Developer 2021 – present

- Key responsibilities:
- Make Web Application & Mobile Application
- Tools Use [HTM, Css, Bootstrap, jquery, Laravel, Api, Git, Adob Xd]

Complete Project| Full Stack Developer (Top 10) Project

- Enaba Almanasek
 https://enabatalmanasek.com/
- Education (Laravel, Reacts) https://baseerat.saidapp.work/
- Hotel (Management) App https://nadel.sa/
- Food Cart (Laravel)
 https://hbilalkhan22.github.io/#/
- portfolio(Laravel) https://mshahzeb.com/
- Ecommerce (Laravel) https://demo.saidcart.com/
- Website (Bootstrap) http://expaninno.orangespark.net/
- Software House Website (Bootstrap) https://orangespark.net/(Bootstrap)
- Ecommerce (Laravel) https://soul-boutiques.com/